A NETFLIX SERIES
[whirring]
[upbeat music playing]
CONNECTING TO SURVEILLANCE CAMERA
[Léa] Ah! So, hot.
Oh!
I'm gonna be late for squash.
- [phone pings]
- [blows air]
DRIKO TAGGED YOU ON A PHOTO
123 PEOPLE LIKED YOUR PHOTO
MY FUTURE STAR
WILL BE QUEEN V'S OPENING ACT
MOM
COME BACK TO WORK AT THE RESTAURANT,
STOP THAT WHOLE SINGING MADNESS!
[sighs]
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
STOP MESSAGING ME
TO: DRIKO PRODUCER
THIS OUTFIT FOR TONIGHT?
NO! I SAID SEXY!
[inhales, exhales]
FROM ADRIEN TO GUILLAUME
BEST BUGS BUNNY CHALLENGES
Since when is he into that?
[upbeat music continues playing]
You're not sending that to Guillaume,
are you?
No.
[message sending sound]
- [phone ringing]
- [sighs]
[scoffs]
- How are you, darling?
- Fine.
- Aren't you at the hotel?
- No, I'm off today.
- [Dad] Is that Léa?
- Hi, Dad.
So, have you done the latest update
on your iPhone?
- Uh, no.
- Do it!
Otherwise, your phone won't be performing
to its maximum ability.
Really?
- Ah! I'm back on. Take care, darling.
- Okay.
Hmm. Your dad can talk. He hasn't done
the latest update on his vision.
I had a new haircut two days ago
and he still hasn't noticed.
- Mm-hm.
- Anyway, the reason for my call is to talk
to you about a dating app
that sounds great.
Tindere, do you know it?
Right, it's Tinder. Tinder, Mom, okay.
And yes, of course, I know it.
And no, I've already told you, I'm fine.
So, stop. I don't need this.
Honestly, Léa, you should try it.
My friend from the gym is having a blast.
She's sleeping with this young man,
loads of small asses, big...
Ah, la, la, la! That's just embarrassing,
so I'm going to hang up now, Mom.
- Léa, please don't...
- See you.
[sighs]
SEARCHING
GUILLAUME CACOLET
USER NOT FOUND
Huh?
[upbeat music playing]
CAMERA NOT FOUND
What's going on?
WRONG PASSWORD
Oh, shit! What's happening? Goddammit.
- Guillaume has disappeared.
- ...this is best served cold. Hello, Léa.
- And so, what I like to do...
- Guillaume has disappeared.
- Please, pay attention to me.
- No...
Oh, sorry. It's my friend
who has a little problem with manners.
Léa, I've told you 15 times,
when I'm with a customer, don't bother...
Guillaume disappeared from social media.
Plus, I can't connect
to his mailbox anymore.
Why are you hacking your ex's email?
What's wrong with you? Who does that?
Well, everybody does that.
- Jesus.
- It's fine. I mean, right, ma'am?
- No, we don't.
- Yes, everyone does that.
- Really?
- See? So, something's wrong with my phone.
Um, I need you to check his Instagram.
- Please?
- [sighs]
I hope that he's okay.
- I can see him. Yes, I could see him.
- You can see him?
Yes, you can. Fuck, that's crazy.
That means the issue
really comes from my phone.
So, it's not letting me connect
to his profile.
No, Léa. You're phone's fine.
He just blocked you.
- What? I don't think so.
- Yes.
- Well, no, I know him really well.
- He has.
I mean, all those years.
No, that's impossible.
He wouldn't do that to me.
No, to me? No. No, no.
- Yes.
- [Léa] I don't think so. No, no, no.
He wouldn't do that to me.
No, no!
- Well, clearly he blocked her. Right?
- [woman] Yeah.
No, no! No!
- Yeah.
- Yes!
No! No! No! No!
- No! No!
- Ma'am?
- No...
- [alarm beeps]
No! No! No! No!
- Guillaume!
- [tapping on glass]
- Guillaume! I don't believe you block me!
- [woman] Who is that?
- Um, it's, uh... It's nothing.
- [Léa speaking indistinctly]
...that I love you...
Fuck, I cannot believe this chic.
- [muffled chatter]
- [thuds]
DRIKO PRODUCER
WHAT A STAR!
SO PRETTY
LOL HER SONG SUCKS
[in French]
♪ Okay, Shaya! ♪
♪ In the hood, get into the circle
Let's do this freestyle ♪
- ♪ Yes, so much courage ♪
- [sighs]
♪ You prefer denial ♪
♪ Fed by cowards you won't even pretend ♪
♪ You'd rather be selfish
As long as it pays ♪
♪ Artist of a system
That dares the worst ♪
♪ Stop all the crap, your stories
Stupid ideas, you wanted music ♪
♪ And exclude me, but I'm stable
Don't try to imitate me ♪
♪ I have unlimited cash
You want to buy me... ♪
[in English]
There, that's your meal.
Ah... cool but these are leftovers.
Someone else's leftovers.
Ah, no. It would be your diet
until you lose that flab on your arm.
[jabbering]
It's ugly.
And wear this under your dress.
Mm... a fake butt. Awesome.
What? Are you planning on getting
a bigger ass by tonight?
[sighs]
- No.
- Right.
See you later.
[dance music playing]
[in French]
♪ I hear your name ♪
♪ On all the radio channels ♪
♪ I'm caught in your spell ♪
♪ In your world ♪
♪ But I feel like ♪
♪ There's a problem ♪
♪ I follow my guts even if I love you ♪
♪ I think this is the end ♪
♪ We'd better go long-distance ♪
♪ You're making me spark ♪
- ♪ You make me pretty ♪
- [in English] Draw them in. Do something!
They're bored!
[in French]
♪ You're the only one I think about ♪
- [in English] I don't understand. What?
- Jump like this!
- What?
- Jump like a rock star!
- ♪ Essential... ♪
- Come on, dammit!
- Right now?
- Yes! Now.
There's no point doing it tomorrow
and you better...
- [thuds]
- [groans]
[muffled laughing]
[crowd laughing]
[laughing continues]
Guys, I've calmed down, all right!
This is...
Honestly, this isn't necessary.
There's no need.
Oh, he's so cute.
Guillaume!
Guillaume, I'm here.
Hey, you came for me?
No. I came to file a complaint.
What do you mean?
[chuckles]
You told them you knew me at least.
Dammit, Léa. We broke up a year ago!
It's clear that I don't love you anymore.
Well... no. That's a weird thing to say.
Wait, why do you spend so much time
with my brother if not to see me?
He's been my best friend for 20 years.
I'm not gonna stop seeing him
because we had a thing.
A thing? I mean...
- For eight years...
- You're completely insane!
I see you prowling around my place.
I can't sleep. I'm always scared,
you appear out of nowhere.
What's next, huh?
You break into my house, kidnap me?
You make it sound
like I'm fit to be locked up.
- [Léa chuckles]
- [Guillaume] Yes, that's why I'm here.
Even when we were together,
you spent all your time
posting our life on social media.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm done with you harassing me. I'm...
It's over, Léa.
And I blocked
all your shitty fake profiles.
Jack-the-doggy, Nighttime surfing,
Cyril Coaching too.
Cyril Coaching, that's not even me.
MANON CAPRIANI AND HER FAKE ASS CRASH!
EVEN HER FAKE ASS
COULDN'T STAND HER LAME SONGS
VIEWS, COMMENTS
JUMP!
Aw, I want to die.
- Oh, stop it, Manon.
- [Manon] Ooh, what a disaster!
I'll never get married.
That's for sure. It's all over for me.
- Come on, cousin. Look at me.
- I'm screwed. Yeah, why not.
- Are you nobodies or not nobodies?
- Yes. We are nobodies.
- Louder.
- We are nobodies.
There you go!
Aah!
[snaps]
Mm. Bernie!
Keep the shots coming,
we're gonna get wasted.
[bar music playing]
[bar music intensifies]
[excited shout]
TO GUILLAUME
I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU
- [phone rings]
- [drunken chatter]
Oh, no!
MOM
INCOMING CALL
No!
SORRY, MY BUGS BUNNY SUCKED
Whoa. Oh, no!
[blows raspberry, laughing]
[excited chatter]
[whooping]
[all cheering]
[retches]
[retches, coughs]
[both laughing]
I think we need to put a lot on
because it needs to... really take.
- Are you sure that's a good idea?
- Let's put some more. Come on.
That's the best idea
I've ever had in my entire life.
Do you trust me or not?
Am I your cousin or not?
- Does it hurt when I pull it?
- [Manon] No, you're hurting me.
[chuckles] I'm doing it
just like in those American movies.
Yup. You'll see you're going to be
- incognito. You look great.
- Ah!
- Nobody will recognize you.
- But, nobody ever?
Nobody ever.
Baby, I know you're not answering
cause you're embarrassed.
I told you this whole thing
would end badly.
Tell me when you wanna come home
to Corsica. I'll buy your ticket.
- It makes me happy. Okay?
- Oh, God.
- Oh, I can't stand it anymore.
- Okay. Bye, Patoche.
- She's so exhausting. She tires me.
- Ooh, get out.
Whoa, it's mom, I live in Corsica.
[jabbering]
Ugh! Stay away.
- Say hi to Patoche.
- Stay over there.
- No more Patoche.
- [grunts]
- [chuckling]
- Do it again.
- It's Mom. No more Mom.
- Ugh! Oh, yeah.
- You shouldn't...
- Mother. No more mother.
- A problem? Well, not anymore.
- No problem.
- Ugh, Driko!
- No more Driko.
Why do I push myself to keep this thing
in front of my face like this?
Seriously.
Why don't we leave it in a small box?
Mm-hm, with miniature key.
[gasping]
I got something better.
- [gasping]
- Hey, I'm not done yet.
- [thuds, clanks]
- [shatters]
[Manon laughing]
It's done! No more problems!
And no more Guillaume!
No more problems!
No more problems! There.
[upbeat music playing]
Take that! Ooh!
[laughter]
- Freedom, motherfucker!
- [jabbering]
- I'm the little bird from Twitter.
- [laughing]
[laughing hysterically]
[gasping]
[groans]
Oh, fuck.
What time is it?
[clinks]
Oh, no!
No! Fuck, no!
[heavy breathing, pants]
Oh, fuck! No!
[gasping]
Manon!
[heavy breathing]
[gasping]
Oh, fuck!
- [gasping]
- Léa!
- My hair is green!
- Ooh, it looks bad!
- Thanks. It was your idea!
- Do you have a clock in here?
Oh, fuck! I'm gonna be late for work!
[Léa] No! Oh, fuck!
[pants]
It's 7:48 p.m., we slept all day.
No, it isn't! Calm down.
We never set the time on the oven.
Oh, yeah! I need to get that fixed.
- What, the oven?
- No, my phone.
- No hang on! Wait, wait.
- What? What?
- What?
- One second, I'm thinking.
Stop thinking. We're clearly total morons.
That's messed up, what we did.
I'm not so sure. Maybe not.
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck!
Maybe it was actually a genius idea.
[chuckles]
You're still drunk.
Look at us. Don't you want to start over?
With a clean slate, huh!
Reclaim our fucking dignity!
Yeah.
See, yes! We're onto something!
I swear we're on the right track.
Actually, we need to do uh,
a sort of uh... cure.
Yeah, a cure. You know, like when um...
Like purifying your body,
you know, and mind.
- Like some people do.
- Who are these people, you say?
- Léa.
- Yes?
You can't live your life like this, Léa,
with the sword of Heracles
hanging over your head.
It's Damocles, Manon.
- But it's fine.
- It's Damocles?
- Yeah, it's Damocles.
- I'm an idiot.
I spent my life on the Internet
watching stupid videos when I should
read books. You know, I'm uncultured!
No, you're not.
A little, sure. No!
Who cares, you've got other qualities.
Okay, anyway, I don't see the connection
- with, this sudden idea of doing a detox.
- Detox!
- That's the word!
- No!
- That's what we need to do, Léa.
- No. Still, no.
- Yes.
- No.
Okay.
What if it helps you with Guillaume?
I'm listening.
- If you're off the grid, no more stalking.
- Mm. Yeah.
- You leave him alone.
- Mm-hm.
Well then maybe Guillaume
will agree to withdraw his complaint.
Interesting.
You could start over. Right?
You'd be free.
I would. With wonderful goals.
We need to do this detox.
- We're gonna do it.
- Of course.
You know why? Because I'm tired
of people telling me what to do.
What to say, what to eat,
what to think, what to sing.
Guillaume withdrew his complaint.
Hold on. Hold on.
- That would mean he regrets.
- Maybe!
- Definitely.
- And actually, I'm tired.
- Of wearing those tiny dresses...
- Of course, yeah.
...squeeze like a tight hog.
It doesn't suit me at all. Right?
Oh, Guillaume. He'll invite me
to our favorite restaurant.
The small Japanese joint in Belleville.
We'll toast with two glasses of Rosé.
And he'll look at me in the eyes saying,
that he still loves me,
that we can start again.
And I'll tell him
that I still love him too.
It's going to be crazy, you know.
We'll laugh and we'll cry.
[gasping]
We'll be in love
for the rest of our lives.
[gasps]
It's great.
I'll get back with my ex.
Okay, I'm with you on this detox!
[Gagan laughing]
No. No way you can pull this off, girls.
And for a whole month?
Yeah, just like Dry January.
It doesn't end on the 15th, does it?
Or try Smokeout,
without smoking for a month.
- It's always a month.
- The Summer Body challenge.
- [Léa] Exactly.
- I got it.
[chuckles]
It makes sense.
So, you want me
to look after your stuff, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, that's fine.
I'm... I'm looking forward to it.
[inhales]
Okay. Give me your arm, please.
Don't worry.
Here.
That's... the shop's phone number
so people can reach you.
Yeah, exactly. And you,
you can use my phone here.
- Aah.
Oh, yeah. What a nice guy,
quick thinking, smart guy.
What do you want me to say?
Don't you agree with me.
Yes? Now, get lost.
I have a Tinder date in five minutes.
[scoffs]
It's 10:15 a.m.
Poor thing...
Léa, you do know that us grown-ups
don't only have sex at night,
right, don't you?
No, I know... that.
It's just that it's been a while
since I've done it in the daytime.
- All right.
- Right.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
[chuckles]
They'll never be able to do this.
Oh, no.
No.
Oh, no!
Wait...
[roller door creaks]
[quirky music playing]
- [phone pings]
- [indistinct chatter]
[phone keyboard clicking]
[indistinct chatter echoes]
[suspenseful music]
What the fuck are they doing?
- [car horn honks]
- [car alarm blares]
[pants]
[both groaning]
- I felt completely...
- Naked!
- Yes, completely naked!
- Me too! And all those
- unbearable noises...
- I feel horrible!
- [groans] Why do we do this?
- I don't know!
- Plus nobody knows. That's a nightmare.
- Shit! Hang on. Let's not panic.
- Audrey!
- Yes!
- Let's meet at Audrey's after work.
- She'll let everyone know.
- Yes. She'll help us.
- So, let's do it. That's great. Call me!
- Okay, take care.
- No! You can't call me!
- Well, no.
- Fuck it!
- What a nightmare.
This is going to be really hard, isn't it?
Oh! I know. I got it!
- Let's schedule. Like in the '90s.
- Okay.
I finish at 5:00 p.m, 5:30 p.m. there...
Okay, let's do it.
[man on PA] Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention, please.
There'll be a short delay while we wait
on a traffic signal. Thank you.
[crowd gasping]
Sorry to bother you,
I saw you are on Instagram.
Would you mind searching
for Guillaume Cacolet?
- Crazy lady.
- C-A-C-O-L-E...
[sighs]
- [man plays "La Cucaracha"]
- Yeah!
[exclaims]
Whoo!
[man on PA] Ladies and gentlemen,
due to an accident on the line,
this will be the last stop.
Could all passengers please disembark
from the train? Thank you.
[scatting]
Oh, fuck. Where the hell am I?
Where... fuck!
Fuck.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Could I borrow your phone?
I need to use Maps actually to...
Here. Yes.
[driver] Just to let you know,
I don't take cards. Where are you going?
Uh, I'm going to Riviera Hotel.
No. I can't do that. It's not far enough.
But where is it?
- [quirky music playing]
- [exhales]
[sighs]
[car horn honking]
Oh, okay, all right!
What the fuck have you been doing?
You're unreachable since yesterday,
it won't work like that, okay?
Okay. Listen, Driko...
I need to be honest.
Uh... the uh... the truth is I'm...
I'm just, I'm getting a little bit fed up.
It's like I'm having
a little bit of a clear-out.
- What?
- So, I, well I...
I decided to stop everything.
I'm doing a sort of a fast from my phone.
From social media, technology basically.
I'm doing a little bit of a... a detox.
Are you completely dumb or what?
No, I've had enough.
I don't wanna see people anymore.
They're... they're laughing.
- They're not really laughing at you.
- They are!
No, stop acting like a diva!
Your career is taking off!
This bad buzz is the chance of your life.
To disappear would be suicide!
We need to post more!
Content, content, content! You got it?
And sort your face out,
it won't look good for your shooting.
What shooting?
A commercial for some cordon bleu.
Cordon... cordon bleu?
Yeah, you know the breaded thing
with the ham and cheese.
They want you to be their new muse.
- Me?
- You'll be amazing. Yes, you!
You fell head first, but your career...
[swishes]
...is on!
[scoffs]
Really?
[engine revving]
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Thank you, sorry, sir.
Thank you.
- A tuk tuk? That's a first.
- I know. Yes.
Right, you're super late.
Blanchard is gonna kill you.
You can say what you like
but this is a dream job.
No, I'm kidding.
I'm on Instagram.
My friends are off for the weekend.
I really really wonder where our lives
went wrong.
Especially you, because at least
I have a boyfriend.
[jabbering]
[scoffs]
You know me. I'm honest.
It's Blanchard.
- [Léa] What?
- It's Blanchard.
- [Blanchard] Léa? Léa!
- What?
Yes, Mr. Blanchard.
You're very late. I'm not happy.
You know the drill.
Yes, Mr. Blanchard. On my way.
[Blanchard] Hurry up. We're busy.
[elevator music playing]
[director] Ready?
Right. That's your moment.
- [clicks tongue]
- [director] Okay, smile. Big smile.
And action! Dive!
[splats]
Come on. Smile, Manon. Smile!
There, bigger smile. Yes, very good.
Come on. Smile, smile.
[director] Okay, great, Manon.
More bread crumbs, guys.
- [blows air]
- Bigger smile, Manon.
- [grunts]
- No. Cut!
Okay, let's do that again.
It's not really good enough.
- [woman] Okay, let's get back to position.
- [director] Let's do it.
- I think I've got some in my eye.
- [director] We need more bread crumbs.
Ah, that's great.
You look pretty as a peach.
[spits]
That's disgusting!
This is your contract.
I got you six commercials a year
for five years.
You sign this and bam! Jackpot.
- You'll be Miss French Charcuterie.
- What?
This is for you.
- Are you shitting me?
- No, it's the latest one.
Yes, you are. I told you earlier
I'm doing a phone detox.
You never listen to anything I say.
Yeah. You don't care
about what I tell you.
You know what, Driko. I think I'm done.
That's it. I'm tired. Enough!
- What are you doing?
- Let me through.
That's it, I'm pissed off! That's enough!
- Calm down a little.
- Yeah! Get off my back!
[Driko] Yes, just lower your voice.
- [director] She's coming back, right?
- Yeah. Manon?
[panting]
Oh, my gosh.
Stop it!
- What's going on today?
- What's going on with this look?
- What is it? What happened here?
- Upstairs if you don't mind.
- Sure.
- The code, please.
[Manon sighs]
I don't know the code.
- Audrey! Julien!
- Julien!
- Audrey!
What?
- Audrey, come downstairs!
- Yeah, what for?
- [laughs] I don't know, just come down.
- Yeah, but to do what?
- We'll see, I don't know, come down.
- [Audrey] Why though?
Hey just give us the code!
I'm tired, please!
- Who ejaculated on your face?
- Your dad!
- He's dead. It's 3568.
- Thank you.
She doesn't get it.
I wrote down the numbers
for the whole family.
- Now give me the shops one.
- Here.
But could you tell my mother not to call
Gagan's shop every two seconds?
Like whenever she's got crap to tell me.
- No worries.
- However,
I don't mind if you tell Guillaume
about the detox.
Maybe Julien is seeing him too?
- What?
- [Léa] You never know.
And Audrey, uh, just so I know.
Are we whispering on account of Pablo
or because of my selfish brother?
He was on night shift for 48 hours
and since his Ph.D. is coming...
Of course he prefers sleeping
on the couch,
that way he can easily annoy you.
- All right, let's go.
- He pisses me off.
- Thanks for your help.
- No worries.
[Manon] Do you need your towel?
No, don't bother. Keep it. All good.
- [Manon] Okay.
- See you.
Thanks, Audrey.
- Bye!
- [snorting, gasping]
- Oh, shit!
- [door slams shut]
HI EVERYONE! LÉA AND MANON ARE GOING
ON A DIGITAL DETOX FOR A MONTH.
NO PHONE, NO COMPUTERS.
YOU CAN USE THIS NUMBER TO CALL THEM:
01 90 00 24 48
Yeah, sure.
[scoffs]
Cell phone detox?
What is this world coming to?
[quirky music playing]
FAMILY
5 NEW MESSAGES
Alarm clock.
- There.
- Notebooks, paper, calendar.
- [Manon] I want this one.
This little one is so cute.
Post-it notes, pens.
[both gasping]
Envelopes, because I think that's...
- He's right, Pat. They're ridiculous.
- [baby crying]
And my sister is doing anything
to get noticed, as usual.
- [sighs]
- [baby wailing]
You okay, sweetheart?
- How much for those two, sir?
- Thirty euros.
- A small discount?
- No.
Okay.
[quirky music continues]
So, cool.
[chuckles]
Do you know
how the sardine can was invented?
- Do you know? Me neither.
- No, I don't. In Portugal!
- [phone beeps]
- Note for the end of your detox.
You're buffoons.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Affirmative, my dear Watson!
Boo!
Well, well, well.
What do we have here?
- What is our son up to, my dear Watson?
- [sighs]
Well, given that his Google search
and this is a large A4 paper
with exactly the same text,
I would say this brat is clearly cheating,
Mr. Holmes.
[sniffing]
Hmm, you smell that?
- What are you playing at now?
- Smells like a harsh punishment.
Caught cheating red-handed.
Catastrophic school report,
behavior, whatever.
So, what?
Teachers complaining of unauthorized
cell phone use during class.
- It's time for a raid!
- Affirmative, my dear Watson.
Cell phone.
- [Rime] Cell phone!
- [sighs]
Switch!
- Computer.
- Hey! No. Don't take that.
[Yacine] No! Not the PC!
- Enough PC!
- [Yacine] No!
Nothing for two weeks at least.
Understood.
School vacation's in two days.
You can't do this to me, Dad?
Oh, yes, we can.
And you can thank Léa and Manon.
Because this detox is a great idea.
- Huh?
- [both shushing]
- Can I have my...
- [shushing continues]
Fine!
[sighs]
- Shh!
- Move!
[funk music playing]
[man in low voice]
♪ I'm checking you out ♪
♪ Huh ♪
♪ Looks like you're checking me out too ♪
- [Philippe] Wow!
- Thank you.
Did you say something?
[narration on phone]
Yes, I was just thinking, uh...
Don't you think it's a good idea,
the girls' detox?
Maybe we could do the same.
- At least no screens in bed.
- Okay, if you want.
Where are you going?
What? You said no more screens in bed.
- [door creaks, closes]
- [light clicks]
[alarm buzzing]
[groans]
DAY 1
[sighs]
Ah, I slept so well.
I don't miss it at all. Not one regret.
Yeah. Same for sure. I guess it's true,
the thing about blue light.
- Yes. Of course.
- Mm-hm. Don't I look better?
- I've never seen you look so good.
- Really? Yeah.
- You too.
- [Manon] Thanks.
[Audrey] Hi!
What the hell? Now they'll never
warn us before they visit.
This is an emergency,
so be happy I have your keys.
I have two bad news, one for each of you.
- Who should I start with?
- [phone vibrates, pings]
[smacks lips]
[sighs]
Manon, your mom is coming this weekend.
Impossible. She'd never close
her restaurant for the weekend.
Yes. She called,
she's coming for Julien's Ph.D.
[scoffs]
What are you talking about?
She doesn't give a shit at...
[gasping]
Oh, my God! She's coming for me.
Actually, you're like
a giant notification,
you pop up without warning
even when no one asked you a thing.
- [chuckles]
- I'm glad you find it funny,
'cause the next one won't be
and it's for you.
It's popping up without warning.
It's about Julien's Ph.D. presentation.
[inhales, exhales]
Guillaume's coming.
With a plus one.
With a plus one?
[chuckles]
What does that mean? Who?
Who's the plus one?
Who else could it be, if not me?
I don't understand.
Who is it? It's a girl?
[nervous chuckle]
[chuckling]
Which girl?
[panting]
Okay, who is it, who is it?
I don't understand.
Who? Tell me.
It must be a really good friend.
No, wait, is it a cat?
It's an animal? It's a pussy cat.
Shit, it's a pussy!
Whose pussy is it? Who is it?
Tell me who the fucking plus one is!
- [Manon] No! No! No!
- [Léa] No!
- Léa! Calm down.
- [Léa] Give it to me.
[Manon] Stop, Léa! Take it!
- [Léa] Give it to me!
- [Audrey] I don't have it.
- [Manon] Stop it!
- [Léa] Where is it?
[all] No!
[cracks]
[closing theme music playing]