A NETFLIX SERIES
Léa.
Do you think what happened is normal?
Honestly.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Blanchard.
Please forgive me. I…
My ex is coming with a plus-one,
but I don't know who it is, so I…
You know… I need to…
I'm obsessed.
I don't know who that plus-one is.
Right, I'll…
I'll get it together.
Léa, I do like you, you do good work,
but your detox thing…
What?
Sven told me.
You know how he is. Blunt.
This may come as a shock to you.
But I know what it's like.
I've had addiction problems myself.
With stamps.
Oh, really? Wow!
Must have been hard.
Very. And you can't do it alone.
So I'm giving you a second chance.
My niece has created
this digital detox center.###center:centre:5.39:[raison, minutes]###
Right.
You are registered for this weekend.
The cure or the door.###door:porte:5.47:[exemple, plan]###
-Understood?
-Completely.
I choose the cure. Not the door.###door:porte:5.47:[droit, choses]###
Mom?###Mom:maman:4.74:[week, génie]###
-Hi, honey! How are you?
-Hi, Mom.
It's 11. You're right on time for a toast.
No, thanks.
Too bad for you. It's really good.
So you came for Julien's thesis?
The nerd in the family must be celebrated.###family:famille:5.52:[service, mère]###
Yes, right.
You closed the restaurant on a Friday,
which you never do.
You took a plane to come to Paris
to listen to, let me quote…###plane:avion:4.86:[valeurs, euros]###
"Stentoplasty
in the treatment of traumatic thoracic
and lumbar vertebral factures."
Exactly. This is both fun and fascinating.
Sure.
Mom?###Mom:maman:4.74:[traitement, américaine]###
I know you.
I told you that
that music career was bullshit.###music:musique:5.26:[octobre, chambre]###
So I bought you a plane ticket
to Corsica in three days###days:jours:5.65:[sais, vraiment]###
and it will help you forget your problems!
It's going to be great. You'll see!
We'll get our habits back.###habits:habitude:4.83:[téléphone, petits-enfants]###
Ange at the bar, us in the dining area.
We'll have a new menu.
And I'll buy you a microphone
with glitter, so you sing karaoke.
-It will be great, baby. I can't wait.
-Hold on.
I'm excited.
Listen to me.
You want to ruin your career? Fine.
But give me back the 5,000 euros
you borrowed.
-Got it?
-Yes.
-You have 'til tonight.
-Yes, you'll get it.
Who was it?
That was Cynthia.
The old lady from upstairs.
She lost her cat again, whatever.###cat:chat:4.76:[vendredi, hauteur]###
So I just thought of something
that I need to do.
Let's meet for Julien's thesis.
Okay?
I wanted to go with you.
You'll have to go on your own.
-Okay? Love you.
-Love you.
You'll end up in rehab, alone and chubby.
Just like Drew Barrymore.
I'm sure it's just a buddy.
I don't know what I imagined.
He invited his girlfriend!
I'm sure she's hot and you'll want to die!
-You know me, I'm blunt!
-So I shouldn't go?
You have to go!
And pretend that you have moved on.
-All right.
-But not with that face.
No.
He must have blood in his eyes
when he sees you so pretty.###eyes:yeux:5.31:[octobre, chambre]###
-Yes. Okay.
-Okay?
-You believe it.
-Yes.
-You're a winner.
-Yes?
-Yes.
-Yes who?
-Yes, sir.
It's crazy how I can my find my way
without a phone.
-Eiffel Tower, over there.
-Yes?
-Montmartre, over there.
-Medical school, straight ahead.
-GPS says back here.
So please, follow me.
I don't have all day.###day:jour:5.75:[toi, sais]###
What's with that dress? It's not Cannes!###dress:robe:4.59:[écran, papa]###
-Come on!
-What?
Is it too much?
-Come!
-Tell me!
Wait up.
Be happy I'm here to help.
Is it because of the glitter?
What?
Thank you for coming.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm really stressed.
-Did you see Audrey?
-Yes, but careful with the baby carrier,###baby:bébé:4.81:[croix, prends]###
Pablo might get bowed legs,
just like Don Diego de la Mancha.###legs:jambes:4.51:[stress, restaurant]###
Right, thank you, Mireille.
I'm fine and you?
-Good for you.
-Right.
Congrats.
-You came?
-I did.
I've been thinking about your bedroom.###bedroom:chambre:5.24:[dessus, études]###
Nico is right, green is better.
-See?
-Totally.
-How are you, sis?
-Here comes Léa.
Is that the grocer from down the street?
How handsome.
-What the…
-You didn't say we had to dress up.
-What's that dress?
-I don't know.###dress:robe:4.59:[portable, génie]###
Fuck! People will stare at her now.
-How are you?
-Good.
Hi.
Gagan, here is Mireille, my mother.###mother:mère:5.45:[raison, dessus]###
Hi, ma'am.###ma'am:madame:4.81:[perte, prête]###
Hi.
We could have worn our suits.###suits:costumes:4.01:[lourde, tatouage]###
It was the opportunity to wear them.
Mom, here is Gagan, my boyfriend.###Mom:maman:4.74:[perte, voulais]###
-Fuck!
-Nice to meet you, Gogen.
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
I hope you're staying
for the celebration afterward.
Are you?
Of course!
-I cooked and everything.
-Wouldn't miss it.
Amazing.
You suck, like a lot.
This is amazing. I'm so happy for you.
Should I cancel your appointment
to freeze your eggs?###appointment:rendez-vous:4.92:[données, voulais]###
-You wanted to freeze my eggs?
-Yes, not mine, silly.
I'm desperate.
They shame me in Orléans.
Do you know that all your friends
from high school have kids?
I had to do something. Let's go.
I'm sorry. Where is your name from?
The USA. My mom was born in Baltimore.
Interesting.
On Google, they say it's Indian.
"Happy who was able to know
the causes of things."###things:choses:5.47:[peux, merci]###
Correct.
Who's that from?
-Virgil.
-Virgil?
Virgil.
"Virgil, born around October 15th BC,
under the reign of Augustus."
I saw a remarkable documentary
about this emperor and his fellows.###emperor:empereur:4.54:[restaurant, génération]###
-Yes?
-They used to sodomize each other.
-What?
-Yes, look.
-I've seen it.
-Look!
These are the bas-relief.
-Léa? Please.
-Yes?
-Sorry.
-I need to talk to you.
I'm so sorry.
I panicked.
Please stay. Stay here with me.
-Fine, but it will cost you.
-Okay. Got it.
Wait up. I'll be right back. Julien?
So…
Is Guillaume not coming?
He's late. What's that dress?###dress:robe:4.59:[infos, bar]###
This? It's for Gagan.
He likes it when I'm feminine.
You know what I like?
When you behave. I'm not kidding.
-This is my time.
-"This is my time."
Since you started med school,
your time is all the time, isn't it?
May I?
-Please.
-Thank you for that, really.
Fucking shit!
Overdraft of 693 euros?
Oh, no!
What's that?
I was hacked!
No. That's me.
That's me.
This wasn't me.
It was.
No, me.
All right, so I spent
5,000 euros in one week.###week:semaine:5.42:[peux, aide]###
-The main results…
-Oh, with bricks…###bricks:briques:3.86:[crever, puce]###
-Shush.
-…of stentoplasty
are in the second table.###table:tableau:4.82:[drôle, désolé]###
When is Manon coming?
I don't know.
-…to compare
-Hey, this is not coffee.
-Of course not.
-…to stentoplasty
on populations strictly osteoporotic…
No significant difference was observed###difference:différence:4.9:[vendredi, putain]###
on the analgesic level or in terms
of symptomatic complications.
The superiority of stentoplasty
with a height gain…###height:hauteur:4.79:[vendredi, don]###
-of four meters…
-For real?
…in comparison…
…to vertebroplasty.
The most popular in comparison
to kyphoplasty###kyphoplasty:cyphoplastie:0.0:[ostéoporotiques, cyphoplastie]###
-are in the second table.
-Don't even.###table:tableau:4.82:[bonheur, secondes]###
-Fine.
-With the correction of kyphosis
of 4.2 degrees against 4.5.###degrees:degrés:4.39:[da, comparaison]###
The values are similar
to the ones of other studies###studies:études:5.09:[con, mec]###
-in osteoporotic populations.
-No way?
Phillipe, you think this is the time?
But I don't understand.
Sorry, honey.
Go on.
I'm recording.
The lack of height when…###height:hauteur:4.79:[couleur, génie]###
-I don't have a clue.
-Same.
Yes.
We're good.
What's for today?
Attila, can you read for everyone?
-Phones in your pockets.
-"The hidden face of apps."###-Phones:téléphones:4.1:[relevé, photographe]###
Right. What does it mean?
If it's free, it means you're the product.###product:produit:5.17:[raison, parents]###
Anyone?
Facebook, Apple, Google, Amazon.
They all offer their services
in exchange for your…###exchange:échange:4.74:[couleur, concept]###
Personal data.###data:données:5.08:[putain, chercher]###
Everything you like, think, share,
they collect everything.
Then they sell your data to brands
who target you to buy their stuff.###brands:marques:4.45:[magasin, appareils]###
Do you realize what that means?
They know what pictures you look at,
for how long, what you type
in search engines
like YouPorn and whatnot.
Even the texts you send to your mom.
Even worse. Your mom's texts.
They can access everything.
That data stuff is crazy.###data:données:5.08:[octobre, putain]###
They think we're pigeons.
What can we do?
It's the same for everyone.
Unless we disappear.
If we all disconnect, they can't sell us.
What?
I have an idea.###idea:idée:5.38:[crois, retour]###
"I will maintain them,
and improve them to ensure
the best services I will be asked for."
"I will help my colleagues
and their family in adversity,###family:famille:5.52:[soir, crois]###
and the orders...
...if I fail."
Quit? What do you mean?
One day, I decided to quit.###day:jour:5.75:[mort, oui]###
Screens, the Internet.
I swear I'm so woke now.
-Really?
-Yes.
Because I…
Gagan has been flirting with me
for years, and now I let him in.###years:années:5.63:[mort, ci]###
Yes.
Happiness was right there.###Happiness:bonheur:4.8:[jambes, rendez-vous]###
In front of me.
All right. Great.
-Melanie, what's your job?
-I take pictures of vegetables.###vegetables:légumes:4.27:[écrans, congé]###
-Here's my work.
-Vegetables?###-Vegetables:légumes:4.27:[auras, ingénieur]###
-Incredible.
-This is my favorite.
-Awesome.
-Yes.
-I love it.
-Really?
In my shop, I have organic vegetables.
How funny.###vegetables:légumes:4.27:[billet, champagne]###
-No way?
-I swear.
-So funny. I could take pictures.
-Yes.###pictures:photos:5.1:[hein, carte]###
Totally, I'm up for it.
How about tomorrow?###tomorrow:demain:5.14:[études, chance]###
Definitely. Tomorrow it is.###Tomorrow:demain:5.14:[courant, regarde]###
No?
-Not tomorrow?
-No.###tomorrow:demain:5.14:[salle, services]###
-No, not tomorrow. Busy.
-Too bad.###tomorrow:demain:5.14:[photo, confiance]###
-We have to go to…
-The store.
-To get a new couch.
-Okay.###couch:canapé:4.15:[adieu, com]###
-Couple's couch.
-Let's congratulate Julien.###couch:canapé:4.15:[cure, challenge]###
-Pleasure.
-All right.
It was super nice to meet you,
and Léa, kudos on the dress.###dress:robe:4.59:[jambes, appels]###
It was really bold. Good for you, girl.
See you.
Not so…
-What?
-She's not so…
-What?###-She:elle:6.49:[tu, me]###
-Come on!
-Okay, she is.
-We are not pigeons!
-Are you Yacine?
That's me.
I just wanted to say
I love your idea of detox.###idea:idée:5.38:[femmes, plan]###
It's a great idea to show our generation
is not all about that.###generation:génération:4.71:[savez, tableau]###
Cool.
So, what's the idea? To drop phones
and computers during the break?###phones:téléphone:5.0:[salle, chemin]###
Yes, you post a picture of you
on Insta with #werenotpigeons
and you turn it off.
All right.
See you in 15 days.###days:jours:5.65:[merci, question]###
-We are not pigeons!
Bye.
Yes.
Yes. Oh, god.
The party is ready.
Coming!
Hey! Come here.
Hey, where were you?
Do you have 5,000 euros by any chance?
Of course.
-Really?
-Of course not.
I'm broke and this close to losing my job.
Why?
-A problem?
-No worries. Just a thing with Driko.###problem:problème:5.41:[grand-père, accord]###
-All right. I'm going back.
-Yes.
What's this? I mean, the dress.###dress:robe:4.59:[pote, min]###
-It's a dress.
-Sure. And with Guillaume?###dress:robe:4.59:[savez, effort]###
It's great. I think he's jealous.
See you.
Right.
Daddy is a doctor now. He got his thesis.
Now, he can finally
take his paternity leave.
And mom can go to work.
Don't look.
What? No.
You did right. Yes.
-It's unbelievable.
-Right.
Exactly, Mr. Principal.
-Count on us.
-He is so grounded.
-As soon as he gets home.
-Goodbye.
Go see Aunty Patty.
They're all touchy-feely. It's disgusting.
Look at them.
Ridiculous.
-…a text.
-Look at them.
Julien, look at me.
-A selfie.
-They're ridiculous.
I'm so pissed.
Wait a minute.
-Fine.
-Look at me.
-I think…
-…at ten.
So cute.
-Ouch.
-Sorry.
My cutie pie.
I'm sorry. Please, listen.
Two minutes, please. Thank you.
As you know,
I've been living without screens.###screens:écrans:4.07:[meuf, ordi]###
And it completely freed me.
I'm another person now.###person:personne:5.73:[jours, droit]###
And tonight, I'm off for an offline
weekend in the countryside.
Fun.
And my wish for you
is that you free yourselves too.
Because we're a family,###family:famille:5.52:[idée, exemple]###
and we have barely talked to each other
since Julien's fascinating thesis is over.
Now, that's enough. We take action
and put our gizmos in the box.
Come on. And no discussion.
It's over. Let's be free.
Come on!
Little challenge.
Yes, I think it's a good idea.###idea:idée:5.38:[centre, porte]###
-Anyone?
-I'll do it.
-Here.
-Give your box.
Yes.
You do it.
-Why?
-Because it's fun.
-Well…
-Come on.
-It'll be fun.
-Let's try.
I'm glad.
-Here.
-Perfect.
-Come on, you two.
-Good job!
-Great job!
-To make Léa happy.
-For once.
-It's not easy.
Smartass.
Great. Dad?
Your timing is not great
because I have chess at 7 p.m.###chess:échecs:4.02:[canapé, gain]###
If you want to play,
there are plenty of board games.###games:jeux:5.18:[musique, photo]###
You could play with your grandchildren.###grandchildren:petits-enfants:5.0:[attention, cœur]###
Lyna too. It's over.
You're going to feel so free.
-Can I get the box?
-Yes!
Wait up, Léa. Sorry, I just wanted to say
I think your detox thing is dope.
Yes, really. And I know it's not easy,
you probably want to relapse sometimes.
I know what I'm talking about.
You've been through a digital detox?
Vaginal.
-What?
-I used to be a nymphomaniac.
-I see.
-Now, I'm cured, I've moved on and…
And it's cool. But…
Yes, I'm proud of myself.
You'll see,
you'll be proud of you too, one day.###day:jour:5.75:[années, lieu]###
Right, I'll stop bothering you.
See you.
Yes. I'm coming!
You were here?
-Yes.
-That's awesome. You packed?
-You're ready to leave? Great!
-No. Not at all.
I have to tell you.
I can't work at the restaurant.
Why not?
As I told you, I'm doing a detox
with Léa for a month.
And I can't leave her,
since we promised to support each other.
But of course, you're right.
That's a lot more important
than your lonely mother.###mother:mère:5.45:[tour, centre]###
Mom, stop it. I'm not abandoning you.
A little.
Okay, I'll come home. But after my detox.
-All right?
-Promise?
Yes.
Baby!
You coming back is the greatest thing
that could happen to me.
-You know that, right?
-I do.
-You do?
-Really?
-Yes.
-You know it.
I need to grab another bottle.
Julien's champagne is gross.
-I see.
-What a cheapskate!###cheapskate:radin:3.07:[burgers, karaoké]###
Okay.
-This is good.
-You forgot this.
And this.
I can give you 700 euros.
What? For all that?
I need 5,000.
But you didn't see everything.
This! The fake ass.
It's silicon. Touch it.
Maybe you can get more on the Internet,
but here, take it or leave it.
So?
-I'll leave it.
-Here you go.
Good.
So…
€700.
-Thank you.
-Good day!###day:jour:5.75:[moment, personne]###
Mireille told me you used to be a lawyer?
Yes. But I quit.
When my grandfather died,
I turned his hardware store into a market.###grandfather:grand-père:5.28:[femmes, musique]###
-I didn't like my job anymore?
-And do you like middle-aged women?###women:femmes:5.45:[côté, fais]###
Very funny joke. I love it.
But I'm going to have to leave you,
Patricia.
I have to go, sorry. Here, take this.
I love that.
-Want to try?
-…so we can have peace.
Guillaume, I… I know
about Melanie and her past.
So…
Just say one word
and I'll cancel everything. Okay?###word:mot:5.22:[crois, tour]###
What "everything"?
Everything. I'll dump Gagan.
One word and I do it.###word:mot:5.22:[ah, hein]###
-And I'm yours.
-Gagan is the…
The guy fighting with the door to flee?###door:porte:5.47:[heures, question]###
Sorry.
Give me two seconds.
Good job!
Wait! Please don't leave me!
I'm begging you.
-I have a date at 7 P.M.
-I know.
I know, but honestly,
you're too old for that.
What are you going to get?
A 25-year-old girl without cellulite
who will give you a titjob?
-Yes.
-But I can give you a titjob myself!
Really?
-Mom!
-No.
I am disgusting. Go!
-Yes? I told you.
-Please, leave.
Hey everyone, can you do that?
-Hey!
-It wasn't me.
Yes!
Awesome!
Nice!
-Melanie!
I can see you, Dad.
How are you?
Fine.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
To hell with it.
Think of your detox.
Look, I won't tell Mom about the iPad,
but please, leave me alone.
It's simple.
Screensaver, of course.
This bitch's phone…
He's her screensaver too.
Obviously. Of course.
They love each other.
So they need to see each other
all the time.
"I love you."
Gagan is not really your boyfriend, is he?
You're still in love with Guillaume.
It unlocked. That's freaking awesome.
Three, two, one,
eat!
Done! I'm done!
Done!
With 11 hamburgers in 7 min
and 45 seconds,
our winner is…###winner:gagnant:4.35:[congé, sortes]###
-Yes!
-What's your name?###name:nom:5.59:[mort, face]###
Patricia.
Patricia!
-Here.
-Thanks.###-Thanks:merci:5.62:[rapport, moment]###
Tell me, do you host another contest
before tonight?###contest:concours:4.9:[attention, week]###
Why? You need money?
Yes.
All bets are off.
Don't come closer!
Beautiful!
Come on!
Let's go!
Go, beast!
Beat them!
-Yes!
-Stupid! Turn around.
What the hell?
No! Turn around.
Turn around!
Dammit.
-Yes!
Here, take this. And that's it. Got it?
-I have like 150 left.
-Hey.
-Ten is missing. You?
-Please.
-Wait, I'm counting my money.
I'm sorry, okay?
But it's life and death. I need money.
Really important.
It's not my fault if I chose
the wrong bunny. But now I get it.
Here's 20 euros.
I know it's going to work.
Doesn't matter. Bunny's cold and sleepy.
So now, beat it! And the 10 euros
is my commission from last time.
It's my first time.
I saw you shoot my rifle at the fest,
so now you shut up and leave.
-Go away.
-Bye.
Twenty missing.
Hi, everyone.
Hi, grandma.
Hi, honey. How was school?
Yes. It was great.
Really? You had a great day?###day:jour:5.75:[mort, lieu]###
Yes.
Good for you.
Because your break is going to be…
Here, baby.
Thanks.###Thanks:merci:5.62:[cours, fais]###
Please, stop.
What kind of break?
-What kind?
-What?
A shitty break. Got it. What did I do?
What did you do? I don't know,
your principal called for disturbance.
You're not coming to Mexico with us.
-No sun!
-No beach!###beach:plage:4.63:[billet, madame]###
-No surfing!
-What?
You'll think twice next time.
I can't stay home for two weeks.
Of course not. It would be too easy.
-You're staying here.
-Detoxing.
Okay? With three meals, two phone calls,###calls:appels:4.4:[magasin, thèse]###
one shower,
and of course, zero screens per day.###day:jour:5.75:[années, peux]###
That's a lot.
They're so strict.
In your face.
2007, let's go.
Wow.
Not great.
Yes, take it.
Great, jerk!
2015.
Come on.
What bullcrap.
She's a fascist nympho!
-What?
-She's a fascist. Look at his torso!
I see a tattoo, but what's the…###tattoo:tatouage:3.86:[ipad, chéri]###
It's a fucking swastika, dad!
-Wait up!
-My god!
-I'm going to expose this bitch!
-Léa!
Look what I found on Melanie's phone!
Léa, why would you do that?
You went through my girl's phone?
-Are you insane?
-I'm so sorry, Melanie.
-It's okay.
-You're not listening.
She's healing.
But wait, you haven't seen the picture.###picture:photo:5.14:[classe, adresse]###
-Nobody cares.
-You shouldn't trust
-this woman. She has secrets.
-Stop it, Léa.
-Go get help!
-I'm sick of it!
We're celebrating my thesis,
but nobody cares!
-Not true!
-Yes, it is!
You're hysterical.
You're stuck on your phone
as if it were a new invention.
And Yacine, hello?
Didn't you miss something?
My thesis! Ten years of studying!
What about Manon? Where is she?
We don't even know!
Anyone care that I'm now a doctor?
-Of course.
-Okay?
It's something! I'm a doctor!
Engineer of living things.
This was my day!
My day!
Julien…
He still throws tantrums?
-Yes.
-Right?
Checkmate.
Phil0355, you lost.
No, I lost.
-Play again?
-I lost.
How are you?
-Good and you?
-Got my money?###money:fric:3.99:[mat, angoisse]###
-Not yet, but… Ouch!
-I said tonight. Was I not clear?
What?
I need to get the keys of Bernard's truck.###keys:clés:4.48:[euro, balles]###
Look, that's Manon.
-What?
-I'll ruin your face!
-The hell?
-I said tonight!
-Let her go!
-Let me go!
-Fuck you!
-Let her go!
-Take this!
-Who's that?
-Bernard.###-Who:qui:6.89:[quoi, oui]###
The bar's owner.
It sucks that I don't have my phone,
nobody will believe me.
Let's give him boobs.
Yes, big boobs.
-A big one and a small one.
-Okay with stretch marks.
What the hell are you doing?
Threaten me again
and the shovel goes in your head.###shovel:pelle:3.68:[gagnante, confrères]###
Ask for one euro from her
and I bury you alive. Got it?
Got it?
Yes. I got it.
-Let's go!
-Motherfucker!
Thanks, Bernard.###Thanks:merci:5.62:[société, tes]###
Just like in a movie.###movie:film:5.36:[chambre, aide]###
Bernard is so cray-cray.
Manon!
Don't leave me here, dammit!
Don't leave me!
-Yes! Bye!
-Help!
Yes!
Manon!
All day long, like a teenager.
You're ridiculous.
That's enough, Mireille!
I want to enjoy my passion for screens.
No limits, no arguing. I want to be free!###screens:écrans:4.07:[angoisse, lourde]###
Do you hear yourself?
-You're going nuts.
-Go to hell!
I've been an accountant for 42 years!###accountant:comptable:4.02:[lourde, préférée]###
Let me do what I want,
the way I want, when I want.
And you'd better do the same
rather than nagging all the time.
Because I won't stop!
Hi, Aunty Patty.
Hey! Don't say Aunty Patty, just Patty.
-How are you?
-Good and you?
So tell me,
have you already dipped your biscuit?
You're so annoying.
So sensitive!
I'm sleeping in the office.###office:bureau:5.04:[services, chercher]###
Hey, Manon was with you, right?
Do you know when she's coming home?
Okay. That looks creepy.
Is it the right address?###address:adresse:4.94:[tableau, con]###
I think so.
I see. It's more on the creepy side
than the paradise side.###paradise:paradis:4.44:[plaît, comparaison]###
Are you sure you want to stay?
It's either this, or having my mom
the whole weekend, so this.
-Right. Fuck.
-What was that?
I don't know.
Holy shit! Be nice.
Nice doggy.
Nice doggy, okay?
Yes, you're a nice doggy.
Subtitle translation by: Hélène Jacquelin